Now it's time for Ebichu's Cousin Akita's corner!
In this corner, we will introduce you to the Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku who have been appointed as PR ambassadors of Akita Prefecture
Akita Binokuni Girls, the PR ambassadors of Akita Prefecture.
We will learn about the charms of Akita and introduce them to you!
The members of Ebichu visited Akita and had various experiences related to Akita.
Akita, and have various experiences related to Akita.
Last time was the first time, wasn't it?
Last time, Yuna Nakamura visited Kakuno Date.
This time, we would like to introduce you to the members here.
First of all, please introduce yourself.
I'm Nonoka Kazami of the Akita Binokuni Girls, number 15 of the Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
It seems like it's been a while.
Well, it's been about a year.
A year?
It's been a while.
If it's been a while, do you remember Hasegawa?
Of course I do.
I was afraid you'd say, "Who are you again?
who's the guy who talks so much? Hasegawa.
I remember you. Nice to meet you.
nice to meet you again. This is the second time we've met.
You said it's been a year, but we went to Nojo, had a basketball game...
That was fun, wasn't it? That was fun.
last time we filmed in March, what was your impression of Akita?
I thought it was cold last time.
Yes, it was quite a bit colder in April.
I thought the cherry blossoms would be in bloom, but they're already gone.
That's right.
I don't know.
The weather was beautiful today.
It was so refreshing.
It's already gloomy in Tokyo these days.
I see.
The temperature was quite high, so it was nice and cool.
It was nice and cool.
It was nice and refreshing.
I guess you could feel a bit of a breath of fresh air.
By the way, the location of the filming...
We were shooting in coastal areas.
So in that sense, the wind...
That's right.
I'm sure it will be.
Once again...
I'd like to talk about your personal life.
I'd like to touch on some of your personal aspects.
I've been reading your instagram and your blog.
Thank you very much.
First of all, you graduated from junior high school this spring, right?
Yes, I'm a JK now.
I see.
From JC to JK?
That's right. I'm Hanano JK. You call yourself Hanano?
I've always admired you.
I see. Have things changed?
Yes, it's different. From junior high to high school.
I thought it would be different, but nothing has changed.
I'm wondering what I'm going to do if I stay here until junior year.
But you've always been a strong girl, Non-chan.
I really think so, so I'm sure you'll be fine.
I hope we can make friends.
From now on.
You're right.
I can't talk to him, but don't worry, I'll try to be brave and do my best.
I know you spend a lot of time at home, but I heard you like gyoza (Chinese dumplings).
I don't have any food I don't like.
Eggplant.
I like eggplant in miso soup and eggplant and meat stir-fried with miso.
I love eggplant.
I love eggplant, especially grilled eggplant with meat on top.
My mom makes it for me.
My mom makes it for me, but there's a dish like that.
I eat it with ponzu (Japanese sauce made from soy sauce and citrus juice) on it.
It's really delicious.
It looks really delicious.
And the quality is like an izakaya menu.
It's good.
Yes, it's delicious!
My mother loves eggplant, too.
Delicious, isn't it?Delicious, isn't it?
I can say that the taste of eggplant is about to become more exciting.
And so on and so forth.
After all, you are busy with the start of the shrimp middle school!
After all, the new song of private shrimp middle school
How about today?
This is May 3rd
Congratulations on the release on Wednesday!
It's a really nice song, and it's been available on various sites since Friday, April 14.
How are you doing today? How are you today?
How are you today? The lyrics of the song are very impressive, and the music video is very cute.
The music video is really cute, isn't it?
Thank you very much for watching it.
Was there anything memorable when you were filming? Yes, this was my first mv in 12 years, so it was a lot of fun, but there was a dance scene at the end that we had to shoot with extras, and we recruited extras from the family.
Yes, so we actually recruited extras from the family.
So we actually saw the real family members dressed a little more nicely and with masks taken off.
It was the first time we saw them with their masks off.
There were so many people who looked like this.
Everyone was dancing to the beat.
I have the impression that it was a lot of fun.
The sense of togetherness was amazing.
Yes, I really made eye contact with everyone while shooting.
I felt that a very happy atmosphere was created there.
Like a motorcycle.
Yes, that's right.
And the cute dance moves.
And Feng Shui's sewing machine.
The pictures were so beautiful that I wondered if Feng Shui was actually a sewing machine operator.
I would like you to watch the music video as well.
And the 10-member Shiritsu Ebi's Junior High School Spring Tour is now underway!
Shiritsu Ebizu Chugakko Spring Tour 2023 100% Ebizumu
The tour started on April 15th in Chiba prefecture.
How do you feel after the performances in Chiba and just the other day in Tokyo?
Well, this is our first spring tour as 10 members and the title of the tour is "100% Ebizum", so I hope this spring tour will be a live show where we can understand how we are going to go as 10 members.
This will be the second spring tour for me too, so we're going to improve on the things we regretted last year that we couldn't do last year, and we're going to make it better and better this spring tour.
I hope we can make it a spring tour where we can say that we really had a good time at the final show.
I feel like I'm interviewing Shohei Otani.
You don't have to be sorry anymore.
I think it was wonderful.
Now that the show is over...
I'm very happy as a person from Akita, because in May, we're going to be in Iwate, Tohoku.
The festival will be held in Iwate Prefecture in Tohoku.
How do you feel about it?
Yes, I am.
I'm really looking forward to it, and I think it's quite difficult for people from Tohoku to come to Tokyo, so I'd like to say hello to the people of Tohoku that there are 10 of us here.
I'd like to greet 10 more people from Tohoku...
Yes, and I also want to eat delicious food.
Of course, we would like you to enjoy the food and we will write up a JK paper about it.
I'm sure there are many people who are really looking forward to visiting Iwate Prefecture.
I'm sure there are a lot of people who are really looking forward to seeing you here in Iwate as well.
Now then, this time I'd like to introduce my cousin Ishigakida from Ebichu, Kazamino Noka, and his wife, Murakami-sama, who is a baseball player and a baseball player.
Akita is not Murakami-sama of baseball, but the place where that god is located, so you can experience the dynamic and delicate taste.
We experienced and came into contact with sea creatures, right?
Yes, it was a very, very enjoyable experience!
Now, please listen to this.
Akita Itokoshi
Now, let's see...
Itokoshi Akita of Ebichu, this is the first time in the new year.
It's been about a year since my last appearance.
This is Mr. Kazami of Ebi Junior High School.
Mr. Kazami, please give my regards to you.
Pleased to meet you.
Yes.
It's a little bit windy here in the creek, but it's really sunny and I'm a rainy girl.
I'm a rain woman, so I was a little worried, but it's so nice to see the sun shining today.
I'm going to be a woman of sunshine from now on.
I visited this time because it's famous for "Nama Hage", that's right, you know "Nocha Nama Hage", right?
Of course I do. Do you know what it's called? The classic. Are there any bad kids here?
I don't say it like that, but it's like that...
This is the first time I've visited Ebichu's Itokoshi Akita for a location shoot.
Thank you very much for your time, it's a little late for this, so I'm sorry to bother you. This is the first time for me to visit here on location.
This is where we first arrived... a popular restaurant specializing in a certain cuisine where reservations are a must.
It's a new restaurant with a nice atmosphere, isn't it?
And the cuisine they serve here looks bold, but the taste is delicate.
I'm curious. I'm curious about how bold and delicate it is.
Naturally, here's a quiz. Quiz!
At Midoko, the ingredients are placed in wooden vats and boiled in a unique and dynamic way.
What is this method?
I don't know, but I've heard of this snack before.
I think it's a salted fish dish, but I don't know...I think it's a grilled dish, but what do you think?
What do you think?
Congratulations! You're right, it is Ishiyaki cuisine.
So, if you want to eat Ishiyaki cuisine, which is bold yet delicate in flavor, or not...
I want to eat it!
I really want to eat it. You're getting better at the latter half of the sentence, aren't you?
Let's go to the restaurant right away.
Let's go to the restaurant this time.
Mr. Kasami will be treating us to Ishiyaki cuisine.
Fresh seafood from off the coast of Akita, such as sea bream.
And it's served in a wooden tub made of Akita cedar, along with the soup.
Inside the vat, a stone is heated to 800 degrees Celsius.
And when it boils all at once...
800 degrees! I can't imagine.
It's unimaginable. It's so hot.
That kind of dynamic stone-broiled food and...
So that's what it's all about.
Wow, I'm looking forward to it!
It's also very strange to put hot stones in it.
Yes, it is! It's my first time!
I wonder what it's like. I'm really curious.
It's very rare.
Why do you put heated stones in?
There have been fishermen in the creek for a long time.
They put their fish and seaweed in a wooden bucket filled with water.
Then they'd heat the pebbles over a charcoal fire until they were red hot and throw them in.
And they would cook it all at once and eat it for lunch.
That's how it is said to have happened.
The culture was taken over by Mr. Takashi Narumi, the owner of Tenshu.
Takashi Narumi, the owner of Tenshu, opened a new restaurant specializing in Ishiyaki in 2008.
We will now turn the discussion over to Mr. Takashi Narumi, the owner of Tenshu.
Mr. Narumi, please give us a hand.
Thank you very much.
Please tell us about your specialties.
The key is, of course, the freshness of the fish.
Freshness is important, isn't it?
Yes, I think so.
And also the seasoning.
We only use natural firewood, so we use salt seasoning.
What are the advantages of using stones?
One is that it doesn't get cold easily, and the other is the delicate heat control.
The stones give a special flavor.
It gives a special flavor.
What kind of stones are used?
It's a lava stone, which is locally called "Kinseki".
The lava stone itself has a sense of history and romance.
So it's a well-selected stone.
Yes, it's hard to crack. It's fireproof.
May I prepare the Ishiyaki cuisine?
Yes, please.
Slowly.
Wow!
Smells good.
It's true, it smells like a rocky beach!
Yes, yes, yes.
I'll go slowly.
Oh!
Ha!
Hee! Wow!
It's boiling in an instant.
I didn't know it could boil like that.
And this steam...
Wow!
The flavor is so good!
That's right.
That's how you feel it.
But the aroma has increased again, hasn't it?
Yes, it does.
How is it here, Onami? It's ready to eat.
It's already cooked through, so it's ready to eat.
Please, enjoy your meal.
Bon appétit.
Manabi-ita Ishiyaki Cuisine.
This is my first time.
The meat and broth.
Bon appétit!
They served it well!
Bon appétit! It looks hot!
Yum!Yum!
Delicious!
The moment I put it in my mouth, it started to boil a little bit.
It's so good! I was so surprised! It really has a strong fish taste.
It's delicious. Have some of the broth.
Please try some of the broth.
It's not too thin, not too thick, just perfect.
It's delicious!
I've never had natural chopping stones before.
It's great!
It's like eating Thai food in Tokyo!
It'll be like eating Ora's Thai.
Yes. Eating the body of the fish.
It's delicious.
You said in your voice you're particular about your fish.
Yes. Delicious.
Well, Mr. Kazoe, you enjoyed the food, though.
Well, it was really delicious. All I could say was, "It's delicious.
That's enough. In fact, it was delicious.
And we have been eating quite a bit, and I would like to finish off the meal, you know,
I served it with rice, sea bream, wasabi, sesame seeds, and Oke's broth,
It is said that it is a great dish when served in a chazuke style.
It's absolutely delicious!
It's delicious just by listening to it. It's delicious just by listening to it.
Let's give it a try, shall we?
Okay, I'll give it a try.
Here you go.
Then, please add some sashimi here.
Oh, I see. We have sashimi, too.
This really thick.
So the wild camarca customized ochazuke is ready, right?
Yes, I did. Bon appétit.
Here you go.
Mmm!
Mmmm!
This is delicious.
I can feel it so much. It's delicious. It sure is.
The sesame flavor and wasabi are amazing,
It's so delicious.
Shall we try the sashimi, too?
Yes, let's go to the sashimi part. Let's go to the sashimi part.
Wow! Amazing!
Yum! It's delicious. You can eat as many bowls of rice as you want with this.
I'm sure it's good.
So, thank you, Kazami-san.
Thank you for the food. It was delicious.
I hope you enjoyed it.
This is a dish that reminds me of the history of the creek.
How do you like the Ishiyaki cuisine? Did you enjoy it?
We fried it slowly and happily.
I was even getting a little sleepy.
That's right. I was so relaxed that I even ate all the ochazuke.
It's really filling, isn't it?
Yes, it was. It was delicious.
Oh, my God, there's always another one.
Ah! This is it.
Let's go to a certain place where you can enjoy Akita's marine life all at once.
Yes! Let's go!
Well, Kasami-san, here we are at Gao, Akita's most famous aquarium, Koga Aquarium.
Yay!
The weather has been fine, and the Sea of Japan is very close by.
The waves are really close by, so it's really powerful.
The weather is fine, but there is a salt wind, or rather, a breeze, and Kasami has become a woman of the Sea of Japan.
I can feel it.
It's like the Titanic wind.
Yes, I am.
So, do you go to the aquarium?
I go to the aquarium in Shinagawa about 4 years ago.
Oh, no.
So it has been a long time.
Since it's been 4 years, I was a little excited like in the Olympics.
Yes, I am. I am looking forward to it.
So, let's get started, shall we?
Let's go right away. Let's get started.
This is Ms. Sue from Ogawa Aquarium Gao, who will be showing us around the museum. Please take a good look at the aquarium.
Please give me your best regards.
First of all, this is Gao.
Yes, it is. The Ogawa Aquarium Gao opened in 2004.
Inside the aquarium, there is a facility for the freshization of Akita Prefecture's prefectural fish, the grouper, and polar bears, so please enjoy yourselves this day.The museum is also home to the Akita Prefecture's prefectural fish, the grouper, and a facility that makes polar bears fresh, so please enjoy yourselves to the fullest this day.
Wow, I am looking forward to it.
You are here, just like hugging a polar bear.
Go through the aisle.
The aquarium that awaits you...
Wow!
I haven't been to an aquarium in a while.
I'm so excited!
It's so big, isn't it?
Yes, this is it.
It's called the Xiaogan Sea Tank.
This tank is a reproduction of the sea in Beijing's Koga City.
This tank is 8 meters high.
It is 8 meters high.
The volume of water is about 800 tons.
It holds about 800 tons of water.
How many species are there?
There are about 40 kinds of fish in this tank.
About 40 species of fish.
A lot.
In terms of numbers, there are about 2,000 fish swimming around.
Wow, there's a little stingray in there.
It's so cute.
It's true.
I've been impressed ever since I got on board.
Yes, it is.
Aquariums are fun.
You know, you get so absorbed in it.
You can concentrate on watching the fish.
Next, let's go to the client's exhibit, the one you've been waiting for.
Here they are!
It's breeding season for one of our clients.
We have a male and a female pairing, living together.
We have a male and a female pairing, cohabitating.
There may be times when the male and female are not here.
Oh, they're not here.
I guess I'm a little out of sorts today.
It's sunny, so they came out.
There they are, over there.
Oh, it's huge! Big!
Right at the end.
Slow down.
Oh, yes.
Okay, they're coming out.
Oh, there he is.
Sleeping.
He's so cute.
He's sleeping like he's really comfortable.
He's rubbing his head against the log.
He's using it as a pillow.
Wow, he's so cute!
It's the first time I've seen one in person.
My first polar bear.
So cute!
This is where the Okada Prefecture's prefectural fish, the hatahata grouper, is on display.
This is the Hatahata Wave Art Museum, where the Okada Prefecture's prefectural fish, the hatahata, is on display.
Here's the hatahata.
Hatahata hatahata.
Wow!
It's rare to see a small grouper, so it's pretty cute.
They're so cute, swimming around.
And here, you can see the shape of a grouper.
If you look closely, can you see the shape of the grouper hiding in the sand?
Yes, I do.
Groupers have a habit of diving in the sand like this.
They are also called sandfish.
Why do they dive?
There are still many things we don't know.
They dive to protect themselves and to rest.
They dive to protect themselves or to rest.
They dive for a reason.
So, they are like this.
They seem to be very quiet, just like the people of Akita Prefecture.
Yes, they are.
Yes.
I'll show you around now.
This is the new area that opened on March 1.
This is the "Touch Cool" area.
This is an aquarium where you can actually touch the creatures.An aquarium where you can actually touch the creatures!
Yes, please.
This is the part where you want to touch them.
You didn't hesitate to go there.
See, I like it.
Oh!
How does it feel, Nagatoko?
Soft. A little fluffy.
Yes, it's great.
Thank you so much for letting me touch it.
Can you go sea urchin too?
It takes a lot of courage to touch a sea urchin.
Yes, yes.
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, wow! So many reactions!
Don't the spikes hurt? They are spiky, but they don't hurt that much.
I thought it would hurt so much that I would get hurt if I touched them.
Wow! You've never touched a sea urchin before! It's rare to touch sea urchins.
It's fun to touch them with your mother like this, isn't it?
It's a feeding festival!
Wow!
They do all kinds of things.
This is a shark called a tiger shark.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Today, I'd like to have cut-up dancing fish, and some okiyami, please.
Yes, sir.
With tweezers.
Thank you very much.
Please try to roll it up.
Little chin.
You notice it?
Oh, that's a little far, isn't it?
A little too far.
You're noticing the dance, are you?
A little too far, huh?
It's moving.
Oh, here it comes.
Oh, here it comes!
Oh, it ate!
It ate!
After you ate, you came towards Kazami-san, right?
He said, "I ate!
Like a report.
He's moving so fast!
Megumi Kishiki is the only one who has eaten all of her own food.
She came outside again.
There's an adult seal in the front now... doing more during the day.
Oh!
So cute!
So close.
Cute!
He's got a big colon.
And his eyes are round.
Round and round.
It's a bear.
There's a little seal in the back.
This is Omp, born last year.
Oomp!
A little seal.
He's a little one, isn't he?
He's just a baby seal.
So cute!
Look.
Cute!
So cute.
Give me some tummy time.
So cute!
It's so small.
You're so cute.
So cute!
This is Shizuka Hidaya.
This is HIDEYA SHIZUKAO, where we display our "Imakuanarasu" and "Ashikao".
This is an exhibition hall called "HIDEYA SHIZUKAO".
There's a big tank with splashing water
It's a big tank.
Wow, it's big!
Wow!
It's a store.Store.
I just saw you at Nononomaru.
He's fine.
He's so cute!
Oh, he's coming up.
He's on the platform.
He's waving.
So cute.
My name is Tonkichi.
He's a 13-year-old boy.
You've never heard him make that sound before.
Yes, it is.
He's cute.
He's bowing.
And shaking hands.
You can touch it?
Kasumi, do you want to touch it?
He's so cute.
Do you want to touch her?
Amazing.
She's pretty firm, isn't she?
Yes, she's firm.
Oh, wow.
He's cute.
Her eyes are round.
Cute.
Thank you.
Wow, he's so docile.
Cute.
Tonkichi.
It's rare to see them up close.
I've never seen one before.
I've never seen them so up close.
You can even feel their fur.
That's right.
It's cute.
Thank you.
It's "Saboranbe Sharan".
I took my time to look around.
There's a great souvenir corner.
This is the museum store.
We have a lot of original goods.
I hope you will find your own souvenirs!
Was there anything you wanted?
That hatahata pen pouch.
I like unique and interesting pen pouches.
I'm going to high school now.
If I had one, I'm sure my friends would say.
"What's this?
I thought it was really interesting.
I showed them the inside too.
I thought it was really cute.
I love it.
And, Mr. Raw...
I heard you have some news.
We'll be open longer during the Golden Week holidays.
We will be open for business during Golden Week
We will be open for business
Please check our website for more details.
We have a lot of bright news to announce, such as the opening of a new area
There are many bright topics such as the opening of a new area and the birth of sesame fluffy dumplings.
Please come and visit us at Koga Aquarium!
Thank you very much.
There are so many things to see.
I was really healed.
I've never been so healed in my life.
Yes, it is.
Thank you very much.
Come on, Ms. Kazumi.
This time I tasted the Ishiyaki cuisine at Koga
And to the sea creatures connected to the Koga Peninsula
I'm sure you were able to experience the charm of Koga.
I'm sure you were able to feel the charm of Koga.
That's right.
I didn't have much of an image of sweets.
I didn't have much of an image of sweets, but I was surprised to see so many cute fish and other creatures.
I also felt the kindness of the people who made the sweets.
It was a lot of fun!
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.Yes, ma'am.
Perfect comment.
Thank you very much.
So, Mr. Kazami, looking back on the location shoot, how was it?
Well, I had a great time when I came here a year ago, but this time I felt like I got to know a different side of Akita, and it was a lot of fun.
I never thought I would be able to eat such tai in Akita, so it was really delicious.
I had never thought I would be able to eat such a tai in Akita, so it was really delicious and fun.
So, once again, I was able to learn about the history of food and sea creatures in the creek.
I learned a lot.
So, last time, Yuna Nakamura reached level 39.
Yuna Nakamura has raised her level to 39.
Now she has reached level 40!
Congratulations!
You're now in your 40s!
Wow, that's pretty good!
Tomio Hasegawa will be 43 this year.
I'm already approaching my level.
I'm feeling a strange tension.
By the way, in Dracula, you can cast "Machado" up to level 40, right?
So it seems like you're already getting stronger.
That's a great answer.
Oh, wow!
So I'm getting excited, and I'm getting excited.
Now that we've got that out of the way, let's move on to the next section.
After-school panhandling
I said it right!
Mr. Naoto Sasaki from Takeya Baking Company
Mr. Naoto Sasaki from Takeya Baking Company is joining us in the studio.
Please give a hand to Mr. Sasaki.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your continued support.
I'm Mr. Sasaki from Takeya Bakery.
Pleased to meet you.
Have you met Mr. Sasaki and Kazami before?
Yes, it's nice to meet you.
Mr. Sasaki, it seems like we're meeting for the first time more often than not.
I'm always nervous.
I guess that's what happens when there are 10 people in the room.
That's true.
I'd like to go back to such a fresh atmosphere.
Last time Yuna Nakamura actually tried it herself and it was a big hit!
Takeya Bread Omoriyama Zoo's collaboration set was a big hit.
I've seen, bought and eaten it at many stores.
How were the sales?
Thanks to your support, they are selling very well.
It's fun, and I'm sure the children are happy to have it.
We put a lot of effort into the packaging this time.
We are still selling them at supermarkets and other places.
We're still selling it in supermarkets and other places, so we'd appreciate it if you'd take a look.
We want people to pick up the product.
Mr. Nakamura really looked like he was enjoying the food.
He looked so delicious!
So, actually, today...
Ms. Kasumi is going to visit the Koga Aquarium Gao.
She had a wonderful experience with Akita's sea creatures.
It was a wonderful experience.
What do you think, Mr. Sasaki, about a collaboration product with Koga Aquarium Gao?
I was just thinking of the collaboration with Gao of Koga Aquarium.
Sasaki: We have collaborated before.
We've collaborated with Omoriyama Domotsuen this time.
I think it would be good to collaborate on the sea side this time, too.
I'll have to say something about that.
I guess so.
That's how I felt when I said it.
It was a wonderful place and space.
The bread was delicious, too.
Let's see, the new bread products from last time.
There were a lot of attractive products.
This time, too, we have a lineup of new products that are full of deliciousness.
What is the lineup of new products for May, Mr. Sasaki?
Sasaki: This time we have three new products.
In May, we have
Hokkaido Fair
There are 4 products in the Hokkaido Fair, and we have 2 out of them, and the other one is a sweet bean paste with a salty flavor.
We have these three items today, so please enjoy them.
We have three new items for you today... the shredded milk cream French pastry.
I'm sorry, I didn't tell you. It has Hasegawa's name on it.
Let's start with the whipped bean bun.
Whipped anpan... this is one of the items from the Hokkaido Fair.
The whip is made from Hokkaido milk.The whipped cream is whipped with Hokkaido milk.
The red bean paste is of course made with azuki beans from Hokkaido.
And as for the tearable milk cream French bread
It is a soft French bread that is easy to tear into pieces.
It is filled with milk cream made from Hokkaido milk.
It is similar to condensed milk flavor, but we endorse this flavor.
As for the last one, salt dorayaki.
I heard that you went to see the anko (bean paste) maker today.
We mixed a little salt from the Ogawa Peninsula.
The saltiness of the salt is used to enhance the flavor of the red bean paste.
I've gone off on a tangent again, haven't I?
That's great!
It's great!
I'll let you cook the three flavors.
So they actually introduced it to us!
I'd like to taste it right away.
I've heard that you always eat bread before and after live shows to replenish your nutrition.
Hanami-san, do you actually eat a lot of food before and after live shows, and not just bread?
Yes, I do eat a lot of food because I use a lot of energy.
I think it's good to eat a lot of food and bread before and after the concert.
So, I'm raising the bar a little bit here, but may I ask for a store report?
Hey there, Mr. Tea Grass!
Suddenly, the character surprises me!
I'm actually an Edokko, you know.
That's right.
I'm from Tokyo.
Yes.
I've already eaten a lot of TEYANDE.
Then, let's start with "teyande".
What should we do?
It looks so good!
Then, let's start with the whipped bean bun you just introduced.
Let's start with the whipped bean buns you just introduced!
It's a bit large, but please enjoy it. The round shape is a bit impressive.
Let's eat it right away.
Thank you. I asked if I should tear it into pieces.
It's quite doughy and fluffy.
Oh, it's good!
Delicious!
I love the cream!
Yum!
Thank you very much.
I like the cream and also the bean-jam buns.
This bean-jam bun is good with this cream.
Yes, I knew they go well together.
This, how do you call it?
It's mashed sweet bean paste.
It has a mature taste.
It's not too sweet.
That's right.
It looks impressive, but when you try it, you'll find it's very tasty.
The azuki bean paste has a great azuki flavor, so you won't get bored of it.
The bread is light and you can eat a whole loaf with just a bite of it.
The French bread is so easy to slice and dice that it's hard to make the first movement of eating it.
Cream, too.
It's filled with a lot of cream.
Yes, with a little elasticity, just like French bread.
Yes.
I'll take it with gusto.
Mmm.
The cream is very rich.
Yes, it's very well seasoned.
It's like the richness of the milk is following you.
It has a certain depth to it.
Delicious!
You can tear it off, so it's easy to eat.
Yes, it is.
It's in stick form, so I think you can eat it in one hand.
It's good that you can eat it in one hand, because you can tear it off and eat it in one hand.
I'm going to use this list of horizontal characters.
I'm going to end now.
The third one is salt.
The third one is "Dorayaki".
You like Dorayaki?
I like it.
Bon appétit.
Bon appétit!
The dough is fluffy.
It's a little salty.
A little salt.
I'm glad you're right.I'm glad to hear that.
The salt comes in a little more than I expected. I didn't feel the salt at all when I was making the prototype, so I had it adjusted a little bit.
I asked them to adjust it a little so that the salt would come out more clearly, so I could really feel the sweetness of the bean paste.
It really stands out! It's so good!
It makes me want to go back to your place one more time.
I'd like to go there again. I feel like I'll remember it after I eat it.
We had three new items for May. How did you like them, Kazami?
They're all really delicious, and there's a fairly large portion of bread, but they're really good.
Ike, I think I could eat all of them too!
I felt like I could eat it if I talked about it afterwards.
Kaede Yes, that's right.
It's so delicious, I want everyone to try it!
Yes, it was delicious.
Now then, Akira Koishi Ito of Ebichu and Houkago Panhandle!
Mr. Sasaki of Takeda Baking Company, thank you very much again!
Thank you very much!
Okay, that wraps it up.
Mr. Kazami Nonaka, please give a message to your fans, listeners and family members.
Yes, the EBITUAR spring tour is going on, and the movie will be released on May 3, so I hope many people will listen to it and come to the live performance.
This is Kazamino Junior High School of Ebi City, attendance number 15, Akita Minokuni Girls.